the third way to lighten up is sun is
found in psalm 119:105 turn there with
me if you will or it should be up on a
screen the Bible says thy word is a watt
lamp unto my feet and a light unto my
path beloved you and I have the word of
God amen
if you want to lighten up if you want to
lighten up take heed to the Word of God
but I mean the Word of God is like an
anchor it is a light in a dark place and
so God says listen we are living in a
world where people now don't believe
anything to be true everything is a
conspiracy oh if you don't like it it's
fake news man you're just guys lighten
up please all right so bad there is one
thing that is sure and certain and it is
the Word of God Jesus gives us this word
so that we can lighten up we can live in
truth in a world of darkness in a world
of error not only beloved does the Word
of God
allow us to lighten up because it is
truth but we're told in 2nd Peter
chapter 119 we have also a more sure
word of what prophecy where until you do
well that you take heed as unto a light
that shines in a dark place until the
day dawn and the day star arise in your
hearts what am I saying
prophecy beloved allows us to lighten up
but loving when we understand the books
of Daniel the book of Revelation when we
understand our prophetic message we
don't have to live in the same kind of
fear that everyone else is living in
because we know the end of the story but
if we're not studying prophecy and I'm
going to
you something beloved the way many
Adventists are acting right now I don't
know if we have a full grasp of prophecy
because we're cheering for some things
that we should not be cheering for
beloved listen to me gotta understand
that we our faith is in the Word of God
and not promises that people mean so we
have a more sure word of prophecy that
allows us to lighten up because we know
what God says it's gonna happen and if
we're not walking and if we're not
living by the Word of God if we're not
understanding the prophecies and what
God says it's coming we won't know how
to lighten up we'll just be walking in
darkness like so many other people
around us but of it it's time to lighten
up the Bible says but other times and
seasons 1st Thessalonians chapter 5
verse 1 but other times and seasons
brethren you have no need that I write
unto you for yourselves know perfectly
that the day of the Lord so cometh as a
thief in the night for when they shall
say peace and safety then sudden what
destruction comes up comes upon them as
travail upon a woman with child and they
shall not escape but you brethren are
not in what darkness that you should be
or you should that the day should
overtake you as a thief you are the
children of what light and the children
of the day we are not of the night nor
of the darkness so what is the light how
do we light enough we lighten up by
understanding and receiving salvation in
Christ we lighten up by receiving the
Holy Spirit we lighten up by
understanding and reading the Word of
God and the spirit of prophecy but there
is